[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "04_getoffbeach",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0401_0100_d_00_container_getoffbeach",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0401_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_getoffbeach",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "S_getoffbeach_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@title_getoffbeach",
        "Description": "@desc_getoffbeach",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@proposal_getoffbeach",
        "InProgressResponse": "@incomplete_getoffbeach",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@complete_available_response_getoffbeach_04",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0401_0101_culldrowned",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0401_0101_d_00_container_culldrowned",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0401_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_culldrowned",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0401_0101_culldrowned_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0401_0101_culldrowned_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0401_0101_culldrowned_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0401_0101_culldrowned_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0401_0101_culldrowned_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0401_0101_culldrowned_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0401_0101_culldrowned_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0401_0102_campandtools",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0401_0102_d_00_container_campandtools",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0401_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_campandtools",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0401_0102_campandtools_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0401_0102_campandtools_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0401_0102_campandtools_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0401_0102_campandtools_proposal_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0401_0102_campandtools_proposal_next",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0401_0102_campandtools_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0401_0102_campandtools_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0401_0103_boarproblem",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 2,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0401_0103_d_00_container_boarproblem",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0401_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_boarproblem",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_campandtools",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0401_0103_boarproblem_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0401_0103_boarproblem_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0401_0103_boarproblem_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0401_0103_boarproblem_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0401_0103_boarproblem_incomplete",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0401_0103_boarproblem_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0401_0103_boarproblem_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0401_0104_xmarksthespot_p1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0401_0104_d_00_container_xmarksthespot_p1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0401_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_xmarksthespot_p1",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0401_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0401_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0401_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0401_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0401_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0401_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0401_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0401_0107_preciouscargo",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0401_0107_d_00_container_preciouscargo",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0401_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_preciouscargo",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0401_0107_preciouscargo_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0401_0107_preciouscargo_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0401_0107_preciouscargo_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0401_0107_preciouscargo_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0401_0107_preciouscargo_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0401_0107_preciouscargo_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0401_0107_preciouscargo_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0401_0108_introtosettlement",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0401_0108_d_00_container_introtosettlement",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0404_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtosettlement",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0401_0108_introtosettlement_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0401_0108_introtosettlement_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0401_0108_introtosettlement_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0401_0108_introtosettlement_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0401_0108_introtosettlement_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0401_0108_introtosettlement_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0401_0108_introtosettlement_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0425_0101_truffles",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0425_0101_d_00_container_truffles",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0425_HerbalistEF_Town",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_truffles",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0425_0101_truffles_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0425_0101_truffles_title",
        "Description": "@0425_0101_truffles_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0425_0101_truffles_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0401_0108_warnmagistrate",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0401_0108_d_00_container_warnmagistrate",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0402_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_warnmagistrate",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0401_0108_warnmagistrate_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0401_0108_warnmagistrate_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0401_0108_warnmagistrate_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0404_0499_TheHermitEF_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0404_0499_TheHermitEF_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0401_0108_warnmagistrate_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0401_0108_warnmagistrate_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0406_0103_hearthandhome",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0406_0103_d_00_container_hearthandhome",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0402_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_hearthhome",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0406_0103_hearthandhome_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0406_0103_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0406_0103_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0406_0103_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0406_0103_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0406_0103_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0406_0103_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0406_0101_intrototrader",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0406_0101_d_00_container_intrototrader",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0402_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_intrototrader",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0406_0101_intrototrader_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0406_0101_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0406_0101_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0406_0101_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0406_0101_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0406_0101_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0406_0101_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0403_0102_introtooverseer",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0403_0102_d_00_container_introtooverseer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0404_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtooverseer",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0403_0102_introtooverseer_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0403_0102_introtooverseer_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0403_0102_introtooverseer_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0403_0102_introtooverseer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0403_0102_introtooverseer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0403_0102_introtooverseer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0403_0102_introtooverseer_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0404_0104_overseersettlement",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0404_0104_d_00_container_overseersettlement",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0404_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_overseersettlement",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtooverseer",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0404_0104_overseersettlement_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0404_0104_overseersettlement_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0404_0104_overseersettlement_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0404_0104_overseersettlement_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0404_0104_overseersettlement_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0404_0104_overseersettlement_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0404_0104_overseersettlement_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0404_0103_introtoartificer",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0404_0103_d_00_container_introtoartificer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0405_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtoartificer",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0404_0103_introtoartificer_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0404_0103_introtoartificer_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0404_0103_introtoartificer_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0404_0103_introtoartificer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0404_0103_introtoartificer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0404_0103_introtoartificer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0404_0103_introtoartificer_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0405_0101_craftforartificer",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0405_0101_d_00_container_craftforartificer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0405_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_craftforartificer",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0405_0101_craftforartificer_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0405_0101_craftforartificer_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0405_0101_craftforartificer_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0405_0101_craftforartificer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0405_0101_craftforartificer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0405_0101_craftforartificer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0405_0101_craftforartificer_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0405_0102_campingunlock",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0405_0102_d_00_container_campingunlock",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_campingunlock",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0405_0102_campingunlock_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0405_0102_campingunlock_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0405_0102_campingunlock_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0405_0102_campingunlock_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0405_0102_campingunlock_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0405_0102_campingunlock_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0405_0102_campingunlock_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0403_0201_survivalistquest",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0403_0201_d_00_container_survivalistquest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_magistratequest",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0403_0201_survivalistquest_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0403_0201_survivalistquest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0403_0201_survivalistquest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0403_0201_survivalistquest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0403_0201_survivalistquest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0403_0201_survivalistquest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0403_0201_survivalistquest_complete_availaible_response",
        "ReleaseEventTags": "HFR"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0403_0201_survivalistquest_V2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0403_0201_d_00_container_survivalistquest_V2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_magistratequest",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0403_0201_survivalistquest_V2_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0403_0201_survivalistquest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0403_0201_survivalistquest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0403_0201_survivalistquest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0403_0201_survivalistquest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0403_0201_survivalistquest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0403_0201_survivalistquest_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0403_0202_returntomagistrate",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 6,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0403_0202_d_00_container_returntomagistrate",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0402_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_returntomagistrate",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0403_0102_returntomagistrate_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0403_0102_returntomagistrate_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0403_0102_returntomagistrate_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0403_0102_returntomagistrate_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0403_0102_returntomagistrate_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0403_0102_returntomagistrate_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0403_0102_returntomagistrate_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0402_0202_introtoallfactions",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 6,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0402_0202_d_00_container_introtoallfactions",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtoallfactions",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0402_0202_introtoallfactions_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0409_0103_timetochoose",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0402_0202_introtoallfactions_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0402_0202_introtoallfactions_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0402_0202_introtoallfactions_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0402_0202_introtoallfactions_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0402_0202_introtoallfactions_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0402_0202_introtoallfactions_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0407_0101_marauderquest1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0407_0101_d_00_container_marauderquest1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0407_Commander",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_marauderquest1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0407_0101_marauderquest1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9804_M_0001_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0407_0101_marauderquest1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0407_0101_marauderquest1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0407_0101_marauderquest1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0407_0101_marauderquest1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0407_0101_marauderquest1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0407_0101_marauderquest1_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0408_0101_syndicatequest1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0408_0101_d_00_container_syndicatequest1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0408_Alchemist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_syndicatequest1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0408_0101_syndicatequest1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9804_S_0001_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0408_0101_syndicatequest1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0408_0101_syndicatequest1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0408_0101_syndicatequest1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0408_0101_syndicatequest1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0408_0101_syndicatequest1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0408_0101_syndicatequest1_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0409_0101_covenantquest1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0409_0101_d_00_container_covenantquest1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0409_Adjudicator",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_covenantquest1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0409_0101_covenantquest1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9804_C_0001_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0409_0101_covenantquest1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0409_0101_covenantquest1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0409_0101_covenantquest1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0409_0101_covenantquest1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0409_0101_covenantquest1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0409_0101_covenantquest1_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0409_0103_timetochoose",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 6,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0409_0103_d_00_container_timetochoose",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtoallfactions",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0409_0103_timetochoose_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0409_0103_timetochoose_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0409_0103_timetochoose_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0409_0103_timetochoose_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0409_0103_timetochoose_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0409_0103_timetochoose_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0402_0401_factionhandoff",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0402_0401_d_00_container_factionhandoff",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0402_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0402_0401_factionhandoff_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0404_0501_encroachingcorruption",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0402_0401_factionhandoff_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0402_0401_factionhandoff_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0402_0401_factionhandoff_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0402_0401_factionhandoff_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0402_0401_factionhandoff_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0404_0501_encroachingcorruption",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0404_0501_d_00_container_encroachingcorruption",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0404_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_encroachingcorruption",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0404_0501_encroachingcorruption_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0404_0499_TheHermitEF",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0404_0501_encroachingcorruption_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0404_0501_encroachingcorruption_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0404_0501_encroachingcorruption_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0404_0501_encroachingcorruption_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0404_0501_encroachingcorruption_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0404_0501_encroachingcorruption_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0422_1501_intrototravel",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0422_1501_d_00_container_intrototravel",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0622_Innkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_intrototravel",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0422_1501_intrototravel_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0422_1502_returntravel",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0422_1501_intrototravel_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0422_1501_intrototravel_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0422_1501_intrototravel_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0422_1501_intrototravel_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0422_1501_intrototravel_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0422_1501_intrototravel_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0422_1502_returntravel",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0422_1502_d_00_container_returntravel",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0422_Innkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "S_returntravel",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0422_1502_returntravel_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0422_1502_returntravel_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0422_1502_returntravel_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0422_1502_returntravel_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0422_1502_returntravel_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0422_1502_returntravel_complete_availaible_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0410_0406_TopOfArcturus",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0410_0406_d_00_Container_TopOfArcturus",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0411_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0410_0406_TopOfArcturus_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0410_0406_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0410_0406_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0410_0406_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0410_0406_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0410_0406_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0410_0406_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0410_0407_OpeningSupply",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0410_0407_d_00_Container_OpeningSupply",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0410_0407_OpeningSupply_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0410_0407_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0410_0407_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0410_0407_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0410_0407_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0410_0407_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0410_0407_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0410_0408_Reclaiming",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0410_0408_d_00_Container_Reclaiming",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0405_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0410_0408_Reclaiming_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0410_0408_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0410_0408_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0410_0408_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0410_0408_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0410_0408_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0410_0408_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0410_0414_Rabbit",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 9,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0410_0414_d_00_Container_Rabbit",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0410_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_encroachingcorruption",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0410_0414_Rabbit_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0410_0414_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0410_0414_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0410_0414_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0410_0414_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0410_0414_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0410_0414_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0405_0404_ArtificersQuarry",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0405_0404_d_00_Container_ArtificersQuarry",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0405_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "04_Quest_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0405_0404_ArtificersQuarry_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0405_0404_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0405_0404_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0405_0404_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0405_0404_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0405_0404_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0405_0404_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0405_0415_Ebenrock",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0405_0415_d_00_Container_Ebenrock",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "04_Quest_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0405_0415_Ebenrock_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0405_0415_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0405_0415_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0405_0415_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0405_0415_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0405_0415_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0405_0415_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0403_0405_AncientProblems",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0403_0405_d_00_Container_AncientProblems",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0411_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "04_Quest_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0403_0405_AncientProblems_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0403_0405_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0403_0405_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0403_0405_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0403_0405_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0403_0405_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0403_0405_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0402_0413_Renee",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0402_0413_d_00_Container_Renee",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0402_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "04_Quest_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0402_0413_Renee_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0402_0413_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0402_0413_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0402_0413_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0402_0413_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0402_0413_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0402_0413_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0402_0401_EnemyOfMyEnemy",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0402_0401_d_00_Container_EnemyOfMyEnemy",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0402_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "04_Quest_16",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0402_0401_EnemyOfMyEnemy_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0402_0401_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0402_0401_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0402_0401_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0402_0401_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0402_0401_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0402_0401_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0404_0402_BreakingDay",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0404_0402_d_00_Container_BreakingDay",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0404_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "04_Quest_15",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0404_0402_BreakingDay_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0404_0402_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0404_0402_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0404_0402_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0404_0402_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0404_0402_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0404_0402_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0404_0403_WhatCameBefore",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0404_0403_d_00_Container_WhatCameBefore",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "04_Quest_16",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0404_0403_WhatCameBefore_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0404_0403_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0404_0403_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0404_0403_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0404_0403_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0404_0403_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0404_0403_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0411_0409_StarsAsOurGuide",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0411_0409_d_00_Container_StarsAsOurGuide",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0411_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "04_Quest_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0411_0409_StarsAsOurGuide_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0411_0409_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0411_0409_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0411_0409_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0411_0409_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0411_0409_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0411_0409_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0402_0502_Tainting",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0402_0502_d_00_Container_Tainting",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0402_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_14",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "04_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0402_0502_Tainting_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0402_0502_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0402_0502_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0402_0502_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0402_0502_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0402_0502_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0402_0502_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0411_0410_UnderStars",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0411_0410_d_00_Container_UnderStars",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0411_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_10",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0411_0410_UnderStars_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0411_0410_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0411_0410_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0411_0410_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0411_0410_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0411_0410_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0411_0410_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0411_0411_LedByStars",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0411_0411_d_00_Container_LedByStars",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0411_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0411_0411_LedByStars_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0411_0411_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0411_0411_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0411_0411_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0411_0411_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0411_0411_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0411_0411_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0411_0101_Constellation",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0411_0101_d_00_Container_Constellation",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0411_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_12",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0411_0101_Constellation_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0411_0101_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0411_0101_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0411_0101_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0411_0101_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0411_0101_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0411_0101_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0411_0412_Center",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0411_0412_d_00_Container_Center",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0411_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_13",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0411_0412_Center_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0411_0412_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0411_0412_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0411_0412_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0411_0412_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0411_0412_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0411_0412_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EverfallArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0404_0499_TheHermitEF",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0404_0499_container_TheHermitEF",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_MSQ_TheHermit_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0404_0499_TheHermitEF_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0404_0499_TheHermitEF_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0404_0499_TheHermitEF_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0404_0499_TheHermitEF_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@NPC_DefaultDialogue_0404_02_Overseer",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_9901_TheHermit_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0411_0413_Amrine",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0411_0413_d_00_Container_Amrine",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0411_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "04_Quest_13",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0411_0413_Amrine_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0411_0413_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0411_0413_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0411_0413_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0411_0413_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0411_0413_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0411_0413_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0411_0414_Shattered",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0411_0414_d_00_container_Shattered",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0411_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "04_Quest_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "04_Quest_18",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0411_0414_Shattered_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0411_0414_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0411_0414_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0411_0414_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0411_0414_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0411_0414_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0411_0414_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_04_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_04_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_04_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_04_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_04_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_04_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_04_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_04_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_04_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0401_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0401_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0402_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0402_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0403_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0403_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0404_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0404_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0405_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0405_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0406_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0406_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0407_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0407_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0408_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0408_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0410_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0410_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0401_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0401_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0402_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0402_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0403_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0403_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0404_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0404_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0405_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0405_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0406_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0406_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0407_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0407_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0408_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0408_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0410_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0410_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0401_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0401_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0402_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0402_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0403_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0403_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0404_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0404_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0405_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0405_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0406_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0406_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0407_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0407_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0408_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0408_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0410_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0410_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0461_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0461_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0462_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0462_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0463_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0463_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0464_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0464_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0465_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0465_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0467_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0467_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0468_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0468_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0469_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0469_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0470_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0470_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0461_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0461_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0462_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0462_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0463_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0463_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0464_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0464_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0465_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0465_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0467_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0467_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0468_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0468_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0469_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0469_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0470_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0470_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0461_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0461_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0462_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0462_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0463_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0463_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0464_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0464_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0465_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0465_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0467_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0467_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0468_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0468_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0469_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0469_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0470_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0470_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_04_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_04_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_H_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_04_H_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_EXP_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_04_EXP_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_EXP_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_04_EXP_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_EXP_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_04_EXP_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    }
]